<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-08T16:23:23+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Lumino City</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/27/lumino-city.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lumino City" /><published>2019-06-27T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-06-27T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/27/lumino-city</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/27/lumino-city.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/97832046&quot;&gt;Trailer&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;http://store.steampowered.com/app/205020/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gog.com/game/lumino_city&quot;&gt;GOG&lt;/a&gt;  | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.humblebundle.com/store/lumino-city&quot;&gt;Humble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Developer: State of Play Games&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Publisher: State of Play Games&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A peaceful, chilled puzzle point &amp;amp; click set in a ridiculously beautiful handcrafted world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only do I have no idea how this game ended up in my library, before I booted it up I knew absolutely nothing about it. But for some reason the name enticed me, so I thought I’d give it a go. And I’m glad I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m usually not into point &amp;amp; clicks. When I play games I almost exclusively use a controller, and when I use my computer for everything else I use keyboard shortcuts. I hate touching the mouse, I find it an awkward and unwieldy interface device. So when I opened up Lumino City and the second thing it did was say “&amp;lt;Click&amp;gt;”, my heart sank (The first thing it said was enter, so I pressed enter and nothing happened). Therefore, it really surprised me how much I loved Lumino City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/c7f2f857c20b17f5aadf7ad677dc200d/eb98a75fe4bb797c-3f/s540x810/400f8203104e65a6d42a294f7d060452cf16b1ea.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;An adorable tiny computer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I’ve just put most of these pictures to show what this game looks like&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of, I know I say this about a lot of games, but it looks amazing. Everything was adorably handmade and just oozes charm. I’m a sucker for tilt-shift, the way it makes the world look tiny, so playing a game set in a world that actually is tiny was wonderful. And not only is it tiny, it’s really interesting: from a house that works as a giant camera to a mechanical boat stuck way up in the sky, this town stuck on the side (and sometimes inside) of a giant rock is odd but in such an endearing way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The puzzle elements are split between normal puzzle game style “work out what things to do, and in what order to do them”, and more physical styles of “figure out where to place these props”. Some of the standard point n click conundrums have a little moon logic to them, but they’re generally pretty sensible; and the physical style ones are often really cool ideas, and a nice change of pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/0518c18e05e925dda29c3a71bade5751/eb98a75fe4bb797c-52/s540x810/e124c51a97384f6f5e11d2cac6faab81bd6c390e.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;One of the physical puzzles (image from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.luminocitygame.com/press/index.php#images&quot;&gt;luminocitygame.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also very well written. Not the story - that barely exists - But all the people you come across have odd but distinctive personalities, and it’s filled with oddball humour. Albeit I feel like some of it was a little highbrow and went straight over my head, but I definitely enjoyed a lot of it and spent quite a bit of my time it giggling like a lemon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/e5a6a792dcb6af6a3a162f678d5fb86e/eb98a75fe4bb797c-8a/s540x810/8c2c5e2c3cedb5781c789ad1d07e6a9521c5a247.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;An adorable tiny ship&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, it feels wonderful. Just everything feels so calm and nice! Even the people who aren’t nice and refuse to help you are still nice. Although the concept feels sinister - some strange men have kidnapped your grandfather and you have to go through a semi-deserted and malfunctioning city to rescue him - the music is so charming, the characters are so charismatic (if a little loopy), and the town is so adorable that the whole place feels warm and welcoming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/197de41105376e7c6ac6dc40d23d7539/eb98a75fe4bb797c-88/s540x810/e5c0f0cbbe4a2b629cfe70fefd9ebbb3bd318ed7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing that did, unfortunately, pull me out of this peaceful environment were some stability issues. Now don’t get me wrong, it’s not unusably crash-happy; and I believe one of the crashes was due to the Geforce overlay, but ~3 crashes in only a 6 hour game is worth noting to me. It wasn’t too annoying as there are relatively frequent autosaves, but it is a little jarring to have a game freeze and have to quit it from the task manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] An adorable handcrafted world&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] An interesting and well designed world that sucks you in to explore it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Lovely chilled background music&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Cute little puzzles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Charming and interesting characters&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[-] The controls, but I guess that’s just a personal qualm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[-] The story I can barely even criticise, it just wasn’t there&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[-] A few minor stability issues&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You should play this if: you like point &amp;amp; click games, arty and attractive games, or noticeably indie passion projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Release date: 3rd of December, 2014&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.luminocitygame.com/&quot;&gt;http://www.luminocitygame.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe title=&quot;vimeo-player&quot; src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/97832046&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;allowfullscreen&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Trailer | Steam | GOG | Humble Developer: State of Play Games Publisher: State of Play Games A peaceful, chilled puzzle point &amp;amp; click set in a ridiculously beautiful handcrafted world.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Last Day Of June</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/24/last-day-of-june.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Last Day Of June" /><published>2019-06-24T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-06-24T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/24/last-day-of-june</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/24/last-day-of-june.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/IDTnDDr0VRg&quot;&gt;Trailer&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/635320/Last_Day_of_June/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.humblebundle.com/store/last-day-of-june&quot;&gt;Humble&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;denied:httpshttps://www.epicgames.com/store/en-US/product/last-day-of-june/home&quot;&gt;Epic Store&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nintendo.com/games/detail/last-day-of-june-switch/&quot;&gt;Switch Store&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.playstation.com/en-gb/product/EP4040-CUSA06073_00-OVOSONICO505GCAR&quot;&gt;PSN UK&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP4040-CUSA06148_00-OVOSONICO505GCAR&quot;&gt;PSN US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developer: Ovosonico  |  Publisher: 505 Games&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A calm and peaceful - but &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; slow - game, possibly the best looking you’ll play in a long while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first glance, this looks like exactly my sort of game. Very pretty, very indie, and telling a slightly ambiguous story without any dialogue. At second glance, however, it seems to turn into a slowly written, third person walking sim with very little actual gameplay. As such, it really surprised me by absolutely winning me over by the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I started this game, I thought it was going to be a feel good sort of thing, pottering about as Carl whilst his life goes well for him with his doting [Girlfriend? Wife? I’m not sure]. So I was very surprised when it became an odd time-travelling puzzle, changing the actions of various people to try to keep this apparently absurdly accident prone man alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks wise, this is one of the most gorgeous games I’ve ever played. It looks like smooth claymation, but if every frame was washed over with watercolours and had the depth of field turned right up. Which albiet I’m sure one could do with Nvidia Ansel filters; but it looks downright wonderful when the game’s designed for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/d6c3943d0950b90e9ffc97c98285b3fb/3777bbba977a7535-c8/s540x810/8a896fda05f7b6fc8eb663a4102cb31ad1e7384e.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Very pretty game&quot; title=&quot;This is such a good looking game.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is such a good looking game.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The puzzles, whilst they definitely could not be construed as difficult, are a very interesting idea. You take control of different people and try to end the day in such a way as they aren’t endangering themselves or Carl - ie. stopping a kid from running onto the road to get his ball back. This is done well, as whilst you may think you’ve solved a day, you’ll have to go back in time to put him in danger again in order to allow someone else to survive, but as you do this, you slowly open up more of the village to find other ways to protect everyone, adding a few metroidvania elements into the mix. And although time travel means there’s the potential for a lot of boring busywork, you don’t have to go back and do the same things repeatedly as once the game realises which choice you’re making, at’ll fade to the next bit so you don’t have to do the same puzzles over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s trying to, I assume, make the world feel very lovely. Everyone has huge heads which is for some reason associated with cuteness, and it’s set in a sweet old-timey little village. If you spin around too fast, Carl gets dizzy ad holds his glasses in a very endearing way. But it does come across as a little terrifying in all honesty. Why is everybody so short? They’re half the height of the doors in this town! Was it built by deceased giants? And what happened to everyone’s eyes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/d707ae6d984cb50df092090d2c7bd73d/3777bbba977a7535-a8/s540x810/f68d90600feabc01ffb84700ad930e3bc6b41389.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Terrifying hollow eyes&quot; title=&quot;Why do they look dead?&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why do they look dead?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a very slow game - that much can’t be argued against. Whilst it’s not a massive map, it is the size of a small village (with apparently only six inhabitants, for reasons that were never explained) and I played most of the game holding down the sprint button. Or jog as it’s called, to fit in with the cutesy æsthetic. It’s also a little over-generous on the cutscenes. Seeing as the whole concept is somewhat groundhog day-esque, you will find yourself watching the same cutscenes several times; and I did end up browsing my RSS feeds during the more common ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/ec2714ce7cb9beb61c6eefece6d42ae4/3777bbba977a7535-5a/s540x810/e8996d15c93a02068b39620b506868a6039e5000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Very short man&quot; title=&quot;Why is he so short? He&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why is he so short? He’s a grown man, and his eyes are level with the door handle.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, what many dialogue-free games do that this doesn’t, is make me want to know more about the world. Inside made me desperate to know what apocalyptic event had befallen the world to turn into the grey distopia that it is, Little Nightmares dragged me into the world of The Maw so much that I bought the comic, Last Day of June made me think “Huh. That was certainly an interesting game.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Watercolour, claymation style graphics&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Interesting and original puzzle design&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Dialogue free story telling&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Calm and peaceful music&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[-] Repeated cutscenes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[-] Slow movement and slow gameplay&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[-] Very simple puzzles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[-] In my opinion, and ending that was both odd, and a bit of a letdown&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You should play this if: you want a calm, slow paced game that’s low energy and looks wonderful, and you don’t mind a bit of repetition and slow storytelling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Release date: 31st of August 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://505games.com/games/last-day-of-june/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IDTnDDr0VRg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;allowfullscreen&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Trailer | Steam | Humble | Epic Store | Switch Store | PSN UK | PSN US Developer: Ovosonico | Publisher: 505 Games A calm and peaceful - but very slow - game, possibly the best looking you’ll play in a long while.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Brothers A Tale Of Two Sons</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/17/brothers-a-tale-of-two-sons.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brothers A Tale Of Two Sons" /><published>2019-06-17T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-06-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/17/brothers-a-tale-of-two-sons</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/17/brothers-a-tale-of-two-sons.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/liftFqr4mbc&quot;&gt;Trailer&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/225080/Brothers__A_Tale_of_Two_Sons/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gog.com/game/brothers_a_tale_of_two_sons&quot;&gt;GOG&lt;/a&gt;  | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.humblebundle.com/store/brothers-a-tale-of-two-sons&quot;&gt;Humble&lt;/a&gt; |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nintendo.com/games/detail/brothers-a-tale-of-two-sons-switch/&quot;&gt;Switch Store&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.playstation.com/en-gb/product/EP4040-CUSA02305_00-BROTHERSLICENSE4&quot;&gt;PSN UK&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP4040-NPUB30989_00-BROTHERSLICENSE0&quot;&gt;PSN US&lt;/a&gt;  |  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-gb/p/brothers-a-tale-of-two-sons/c4q29cmj31nx?activetab=pivot:overviewtab&quot;&gt;XBox Live&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developer: Starbreeze Studios  |  Publisher: 505 Games&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An absolutely incredible game; I cannot recommend it enough. Gorgeous graphics, amazing soundtrack, original mechanics, and one of the best stories I have ever encountered in gaming. One of my top five games of all time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought I’d start this off with one of my favourite games. I know nobody will read this unless they decide to read through all of my stuff [reviews? comments? recommendations?] for posterity, but I’m going to do so anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a massive fan of Scandinavian games, as you’ll come to see, so Brothers wins points off the bat for being directed by a Swede, Josef Fares. It also wins points for the high fantasy setting, which I like when it’s done well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brothers is, I believe, the only example of “singleplayer co-op” as you play as two characters simultaneously. Other people I know have found this a little confusing, but I got to grips with it and found it a fairly intuitive control scheme. The store page claims it requires a controller, but it does in fact have okay keyboard controls. I played it with an Xbone controller. The camera controls are a bit odd, but I never had cause to use them, and one analogue stick for each character and triggers to interact seems to work fine for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/dcbb9ada94d2e6b657cf7228aa7f9272/dec4d47fd261ace9-8a/s540x810/d4d8cd195da3cb909e980c09f4458458d3701a28.png&quot; alt=&quot;Control Scheme image from Google Play Store&quot; title=&quot;One control stick for each brother - Image from android version, so it doesn&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;One control stick for each brother - Image from android version, so it doesn’t look as pretty as the PC version. (&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.and.games505.brothers&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&quot;&gt;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.and.games505.brothers&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cell-shaded look makes the game age well - as it usually does - and for a game released in 2013 (that’s how on the ball these reviews are going to be) it still looks in my opinion much better than many games released this year. Add this to gorgeous environmental design, and the whole thing is just a visual treat even today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/a3bdae76f376c1270fba224d37ae0935/dec4d47fd261ace9-ca/s540x810/7be5575ffe478444c31a47a7c682e831555a4b34.png&quot; alt=&quot;Mines image from Steam page&quot; title=&quot;I think this is pretty gorgeous. (Image from Steam page)&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I think this is pretty gorgeous. (Image from Steam page)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The puzzles are pretty standard far for this type of game: a smaller, lither character for can fit through small gaps, and a stronger character who can swim and lift the younger brother up to higher places. But the game changes things up quite a bit, so one doesn’t really notice. From saving a troll, to avoiding forest wolves, to hang-gliding through a canyon, there’s a decent amount of gameplay variance. I’m trying to avoid spoilers as I believe this game is much better played, but that makes this section quite tricky to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It makes the next section even trickier. The story is based around going on a journey to find medicine for your father (I’m not afraid of spoiling this, it’s in the first five minutes) from a healing tree in a magical forest. This takes the eponymous brothers far away from the safety of the vilage they’ve grown up in; to, amongst other places, a forest of living branches, an abandoned village inhabited by an invisible monster, and an old giant’s battlefield. The story is purely conveyed through the environment and characters, with no dialogue at all apart from the brothers calling each others names.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/7ad5c38b11a2bf584d08f70866b80f56/dec4d47fd261ace9-af/s540x810/b72ef2192feda09a7d09d8b0baf78aa9010ebad5.png&quot; alt=&quot;Brothers sitting down on a bench&quot; title=&quot;It gives one plenty of opportunities just to sit down and enjoy the scenery (Image from https://wallhere.com/en/wallpaper/712709)&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It gives one plenty of opportunities just to sit down and enjoy the scenery (Image from &lt;a href=&quot;https://wallhere.com/en/wallpaper/712709&quot;&gt;https://wallhere.com/en/wallpaper/712709&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a brilliant example of how to build a tale into a game, rather than tacking it on at the end, and really exemplifies the concept of video games as a narrative art form. Well worth playing if you’re even slightly into games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Art design that holds up well and looks fantastic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Unique, ingenuitive control scheme&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Story that ties into the gameplay, rather than just being a vessel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[+] Soundtrack that sits in the background, subtly enhancing the experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[-] Not much. Using the shoulder buttons for camera control, I guess?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Release date: 7th of August 2013&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://505games.com/games/brothers/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/liftFqr4mbc&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;allowfullscreen&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Trailer | Steam | GOG | Humble | Switch Store | PSN UK | PSN US | XBox Live Developer: Starbreeze Studios | Publisher: 505 Games An absolutely incredible game; I cannot recommend it enough. Gorgeous graphics, amazing soundtrack, original mechanics, and one of the best stories I have ever encountered in gaming. One of my top five games of all time.</summary></entry></feed>